本字幕由YYeTs字幕組原創翻譯
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
饑餓
的青春
第二季  第六集
我去上班了
Okay, I'm off to work.
想得美
The hell you are!
怎么了
What?
加比  這地方比你的人生還混亂
Gabi, this place is messier than your life.
我在外面睡覺時  這是我的臥室
Okay, well, when I sleep out here, this is my bedroom.
但你醒來后  這是我們的客廳
Okay, but when you wake up, it is our living room.
好吧
Fine.
打掃好難啊
Cleaning is so hard.
-開心了嗎  -等我們住進兩臥公寓我就開心了
- Happy? - I will be when we get a two-bedroom apartment.
你永遠也不會的
Well, you're never gonna be, then,
因為沒人會離開這棟租金管制大樓
because nobody leaves this rent-controlled building
除非死了被抬出去
unless they're rolled out of here.
天啊
Oh, my god!
這是2B的雅各布森太太
That's Mrs. Jacobsen from 2B.
出什么事了
What happened?
中風
Stroke.
她跌跌撞撞地從主臥室走過客浴室
She stumbled from the master bedroom, through the guest bathroom,
在洗烘衣機上撞到了頭
hit her head on the washer/dryer,
然后在次臥里昏倒
then collapsed in the second bedroom.
死了
Dead.
天啊  難以置信雅各布森太太
Oh, my god, I can't believe Mrs. Jacobsen...
居然有次臥
had a second bedroom!
加比  可憐的雅各布森太太  愿她安息
Gabi, poor Mrs. Jacobsen! May she rest in peace.
是啊  愿我在她的次臥安息
Yes, and may I rest in her second bedroom!
那太刻薄了
Okay, that is so mean.
真的嗎  比你穿褲子她說你是妓女
Really? Meaner than when she called you a whore
還要刻薄嗎
for wearing pants?
對
Oh, that's right.
我們一定要弄到那個死婊子的公寓
We are so getting that dead bitch's apartment.
怎么做啊  這里是舊金山
Well, how? I mean, this is San Francisco.
很難找公寓的
Apartments are really hard to find.
那個醫護人員肯定都申請了那間公寓
I bet that paramedic already has an application in for it.
但我們認識房東啊
Yeah, but we know the landlord.
我們只用說服他租給我們
So, all we gotta do is convince him to give it to us.
我讀過一篇文章
And, I read an article that
說如果你提供食物或者性愛
said you can get anything you want from a man
就可以從男人那得到一切
if you give him food or sex.
你得讀文章才知道這點嗎
You had to read an article to know that?
-我給食物  -等等
- Dibs on food! - Wait!
你給喬什做了這么豐盛的早餐
Wow, you're going all out for Josh's breakfast.
這次又犯了什么錯想彌補啊
What mistake are you making up for this time?
實際上我在做土豆芝士餃討好我的俄羅斯房東
Actually, I'm making pirogies to butter up my Russian landlord.
你不止毀了我們的生活啊
So you don't just screw up our lives?
不  我沒跟你說好消息嗎
No. Didn't I tell you the good news?
走廊對面的女人中風死了
The lady across the hall died of a stroke!
早上好  帥哥美女們
Good morning, beautiful people!
知道誰餓了嗎  我
You know who's starving? Me.
知道為什么嗎  滾床單了
You know why? Sex.
翻譯  冰藍  aaaBao   roaddog
知道有多少次嗎  超多
You know how much? Tons.
校對  roaddog
你知道大家常說中年婦女
You know how they say older women
床技高超  因為她們花樣百出嗎
are awesome 'cause they know all kinds of stuff?
時間軸  aaaBao
是真的
They do.
后期  斯人   總監  roaddog
中年婦女  那幸運的女士是誰
Older women? Who's the lucky lady?
不  你選了她而不是我嗎
No! You picked her over me?
抱歉  艾略特  我有喬什想要的東西
Sorry, Elliot. I got a little something Josh wants.
你有他不想要的東西
You got a little something he doesn't.
我不想要你倆的任何東西
I don't want anything from either of you.
因為我從肖娜身上得到夠多了
Because I'm getting plenty from Shauna.
喬什只是讓我住在這里
Josh is just letting me stay here
因為我跟科爾曼吵架了
'cause I got in a fight with Coleman.
什么  你們剛同居就吵架了嗎
What? You guys just moved in together? You're already fighting?
我知道  但我不喜歡他給女服務員小費的方式
I know. But, I didn't like the way he tipped the waitress.
-他給了她什么  -他的電話
- Oh, what'd he leave her? - His phone number.
好啊  愛人
Hi, lover.
我在跟高個白人說話呢
And I'm talking to the tall, white one.
各位  這是我女朋友
Guys, this is my girlfriend.
天啊  你才不是姑娘  你是肖娜·史蒂文斯
Oh my god, you're not a girl, you're Shauna Stevens!
ABC新聞的科技記者
You're the tech reporter for ABC news.
我男朋友是個程序員
My boyfriend's a programmer,
他床頭貼著你的海報
and he has a poster of you above his bed.
原來那張是他買的啊
Oh, so he's the one who bought that.
她在謙虛
She's being modest.
她實際上得了兩次皮博迪獎
She actually has two Peabody Awards
快速撥號還存了安德森·庫珀的號碼
and Anderson Cooper on speed dial.
我床頭有一張他的海報
I have a poster of him over my bed.
肖娜  我想著
So, Shauna, I was wondering,
今晚去你家過吧
maybe we spend the night at your place, tonight?
我還沒去過呢
You know, I still haven't been there.
不行  我剛請人清潔了地板
Uh, we can't. I just had the floors cleaned,
有點臟
and it's kind of a mess.
我不介意臟[淫蕩]的東西
Well, you know I don't mind things a little bit dirty.
我剛想起來  我家也停水了
Oh, and I just remembered, the water's also been shut off.
也許我們該找人去修
Well, maybe we should call somebody to fix it?
聽說安德森·庫珀很會修水管[JJ]
I hear Anderson Cooper's good with pipes...
肖娜  如果我不了解你
You know, Shauna, if I didn't know any better,
我會覺得你是想隱瞞什么呢
I'd think you were trying to hid something from me?
這樣吧  不如我們之后藏點東西吧
I'll tell you what. How about we hide something later...
今晚見
See you tonight?
她身上有很棒的地方藏東西
Oh, she's got good hiding places.
那是房東
That's the landlord!
他在上來的路上了
He's on his way up.
我的土豆芝士餃準備好了
My pirogies are hot and ready.
我的也是
So are mine.
你看起來美呆了
You look amazing.
但是我覺得你兩邊不一樣高
But, um, I think you're a little lopsided.
這個嘛
Oh, well, you know,
我還沒塞完左胸  咱家的衛生紙就用完了
we ran out of toilet paper before I could finish stuffing lefty.
你怎么這么快就讓他來了啊
So, how'd you get him up here, so fast?
我跟他說水槽堵了
Oh, well, I told him the sink was clogged.
因為我們的枕頭大戰
From all of our pillow fights.
真棒
Great, great.
我這樣問是因為我了解你
Um, I only ask you this because I know you.
你記得去堵水槽了嗎
Did you remember to clog the sink?
-快  放一點衛生紙進去  -天啊
- Quick! Put a little of your bigger boobie in there! - Oh, god!
是他
That's him.
快點快點
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
請進吧
Come in.
姑娘們  哪個水槽堵了啊
Hello, girls. Which sink is clogged?
我覺得水槽可能是我在
I think it may have gotten clogged
做世界聞名的土豆芝士餃時堵塞的
while I was making my world famous pirogies.
你想吃一個嗎
Do you want one?
不想
No.
水槽修好了  我走了
Sink fixed. I go now.
等等
Wait! Um...
我們聽說2B單元對外招租了
We heard that apartment 2B opened up?
大家都想租2B單元
Everyone wants 2B.
住4A的姑娘為了租2B都愿意獻出肉體了
Girl in 4A offered to do disgusting things for 2B.
而且她擁有一對D杯大乳
And she's got two D's.
因為我喪妻
Just because I lost wife
她們就認為可以跟我上床來換那套房子
they think they can sex me for apartment.
真不要臉
Oh, that is pathetic.
我過敏了
I have allergies.
我走了
I go now.
或許我再待一會吧
Or, maybe I stay.
姑娘們  喬什正忙著和女主播親熱
Hey, girls. Josh was getting busy with the anchorwoman.
聲音可不比采訪直升機的動靜小
And the buzz in her hair was not from the news chopper.
我能在這看《法律與秩序》嗎
So, is it cool if I watch Law & Order here?
我超愛看《法律與秩序》
I... I love the Law & Order.
而且我老婆死了
And my wife's dead.
太好了  你倆快進來  請坐
Well, great, come on in, sit down, both of you!
還有什么比邊看《法律與秩序》
Yeah, what goes better with the Law & Order
邊吃餃子更配的呢
than the pirogies?
比如配白俄羅斯雞尾酒[俄羅斯白人]
Maybe a White Russian?
要是有人問  你就說是來問我借車的
Okay, if anybody asks, you're here to borrow my car.
是嗎
Oh, really?
我不是該說我是來騙尤蘭達
I shouldn't say that I'm here to trick Yolanda
跟我們的房東約會
into dating our landlord
好讓我們租到那套房的嗎
so we can get that apartment?
但愿你能把譏諷的話留到
You know, hopefully, you can keep your sarcasm
我們新的步入式衣帽間里說
in our new walk-in closet.
我超想租下那套房
I just really want this.
我是兩臥狂熱愛好者
I have two bedroom fever.
-尤蘭達  -姑娘們
- Hey, Yolanda. - Hey, girls.
-沒什么  我只是來找她借車的  -什么
- Nothing, I'm just here to borrow her car. - What?
你和科爾曼怎么樣了
So, how's it going with Coleman?
你還想讓他在公交車前面走嗎
Do you still want him to walk in front of a bus?
當然不  親愛的
Oh, no, honey.
我想推他迎面撞上公交車
I wanna push him in front of one.
我想到了個主意
Well, you know, I actually just had an idea.
正好想到
Just now.
我覺得需要給科爾曼點教訓
Um, I feel like Coleman needs a taste of his own medicine.
或許你該和別人約會  讓他吃醋
Maybe you should go out with another guy and make him jealous?
真是個好主意  加比  給他個教訓
That's a great idea, Gabi. That'll teach him.
這辦法可行  但有個問題
It would teach him. Only one problem.
要是我認識其他人  就不會跟我前夫約會了
If I knew a guy, I wouldn't date my ex-husband.
我又想到了個主意
Well, I just had another idea.
才想到的
Just now.
你覺得迪米特里怎么樣
Um, what about Dmitri?
又是個好主意  加比
Another great idea, Gabi!
你們性感的俄羅斯房東嗎  那家伙不錯
Your sexy Russian landlord? That guy is fine.
你覺得你們倆能...
You think you two can...
晚上八點  三藩咖啡館  別遲到
Sanfran Cafe 8:00 pm. Don't be late.
跑得如何  姐們
How was your run, mate?
要不要來點剛做好的早餐餐呢
Would you like a spot o' brekkie?
我學了點澳洲俚語  我真貼心
I googled Australian slang. I'm a delight.
能給我杯茶茶嗎
Can I have a cuppa?
這詞的意思是"一杯茶"
That means "cup of tea."
好的  抱歉  我還沒看到C打頭的那些
Oh, right, sorry. I didn't make it to the c's.
加比  你好像跟喬什關系很好
Gabi, you seem close with Josh.
為什么  他跟你說了什么
Why, what'd he tell you?
我開玩笑的  我們關系不錯
I mean, I'm just kidding. We're close.
我能問你個問題嗎
Can I ask you a question?
問題題嗎
A questie?
你覺得暫時對人保守秘密
Do you think it's wrong to keep a secret
是不對的嗎  當然是在
from someone just for a little while
出于善意的情況下
with only good intentions, of course.
你我之間
Well, between you and me,
我都不需要知道是出于善意
I don't even need the good intentions part.
你真是貼心
Yeah, you are a delight.
什么秘密
So, what's the secret?
我是位母親
I'm a mum.
什么  真的嗎
What? You are?
我共享七歲兒子布雷特的撫養權
I share custody of my seven-year-old son, Brett.
我很怕告訴喬什
And, I'm afraid to tell Josh.
這就是我言辭閃爍的原因
That's why I've been acting so dodgy.
"閃爍"  這調子不錯
"Dodgy." That's a good one.
聽著  喬什這個人
Well, listen, about Josh,
我覺得你不用擔心
I don't think you have anything to worry about.
喬什喜歡小孩子[小個子]
Josh loves little guys.
你見過艾略特嗎
You've met Elliot?
你說的對  加比
You're right, Gabi.
現在我只要找個合適的時機告訴他
Now I just need to find the right time to tell him.
為何不在吃完早餐餐后
Why don't you tell him after brekkie,
他喝茶茶的時候告訴他
when he's had a cuppa,
除非你覺得這太閃躲了
unless you think that's too dodgy.
你好
G'day!
喬什  我做壞事了
Josh, I did something bad.
我搞到了安德森·庫珀的電話號碼
I got Anderson Cooper's phone number.
這有什么不好的呢
Why is that bad?
我偷了肖娜的手機才搞到的
I stole Shauna's phone to get it.
-艾略特  -還有更糟的事
- Elliot! - Oh, it gets worse.
在這過程中
In the midst of my mischief making,
我發現肖娜對你不忠
I discovered Shauna is cheating on you.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
我偶然看到了幾條她發給一個
I stumbled upon a few texts she sent
名叫布雷特的男妓的短信
to some manwhore named Brett.
荒唐至極
You're being ridiculous,
而且你侵犯了她的隱私
and you invaded her privacy!
讀給我聽
Read 'em to me.
"我想親親你的臉蛋"
"I miss kissing your face."
這不算什么
That's not so bad.
"等不及爬上床  今晚與你共眠了"
"Can't wait to crawl into bed with you tonight."
性質嚴重了
Getting worse.
"買了一堆新玩具  我們能一起玩"
"Bought a bunch of new toys we can play with together."
天吶
Oh, God.
她也給我買了"玩具"一起玩
She bought us toys to play with, too.
天吶  毛巾加熱器在打折
Oh my God, they got towel warmers on sale.
我該買一個嗎
Should I get one?
不  買兩個  一個浴室放一個
No. Get two. One for each bathroom!
你覺得嗎  我們興奮的太早了
You know what, we're getting too excited about this.
還不知道迪米特里和尤蘭達約會得如何了
We don't even know how Dmitri and Yolanda's date went.
但是他們三小時前就去約會了
But, they left on their date three hours ago.
我能先把它放進購物車嗎
Can I at least just add to cart?
天吶  我們太專注于這件事了
Man, we are obsessing over this.
得找點別的事來做
We gotta find something
好轉移我們對公寓的注意力
that's gonna take our mind of the apartment.
公寓  什么公寓
Apartment. Heh. What apartment?
天吶  不管用
Oh my God, it's not working.
-我們得過去看看  -好的
- We have to go over there! - Okay.
-姑娘們  -迪米特里
- Oh, girls. - Oh, Dmitri.
約會進行得如何
How did your date go?
這是我第一次和人約會
This is first date I've been on.
在我妻子死后
Well, since wife dead.
我還以為再也不會了
I thought it never happen,
-但我戀愛了  -他戀愛了
- But I'm in love! - He's in love!
尤蘭達真的很棒
Yolanda is bee's knees!
是  她的確很棒
Yeah. She is totally bee's knees.
那你還記得你說
So, do you remember that one time
欠我人情那事嗎  我記得
where you said that you owe me? Well, I do.
我就是在想...
Um, I was just wondering,
如果有可能的話
if maybe this could possibly--
-我們想租2B單元  -對
- We want apartment 2B! - Yeah.
姑娘們  你們照應我  我也想著你們
Girls, you scratch my back, I scratch yours...
兩居公寓是你們的了
with two-bedroom apartment!
-耶  -謝謝
- Yay! - Thank you!
這是我從勞改營出來以后最開心的事了
I've not been so happy since release from labor camp.
謝謝你們  謝謝
Thank you, thank you.
我周一把租約帶來
I bring you lease on Monday.
好的
Okay.
公寓是我們的啦
We got the apartment!
肖娜  我有事想跟你聊聊
Shauna, there's something I wanna talk to you about.
不是事后才聊天嗎
Isn't talk what we do after sex?
今晚  我們事前就聊
Well, tonight, we're talking before.
我知道布雷特的事了
I know about Brett.
天啊  你怎么知道的
Oh my god, how'd you find out?
沒關系  喬什  我發誓要告訴你的
That doesn't matter, Josh. I swear I was gonna tell you.
但你沒有
But, you didn't.
我不說是因為我真的很喜歡你
I was holding back because I'm crazy about you.
是嗎
Are you?
是的
Yes.
所以我才很想你們見面
That's why I would love for you to meet him.
見他  布雷特嗎
Meet him? Brett?
為...什么
Why... why?
因為你們是我生命里的兩個男人
Because you're the two men in my life.
你覺得我們三個找時間玩玩可以嗎
How would you feel if the three of us had a little playdate?
"玩...玩"嗎
A play what now?
好吧
Uh, okay.
你想讓布雷特過來
You want Brett to come here.
和我們兩個玩嗎
And play with me and you?
我們三個一起
All of us together.
一起哈...一起
Together... wow, together...
喬什  我知道這不太好接受
Look, Josh, I know this is a lot to take in.
但如果你不喜歡
But, if you're not into it,
很抱歉  我們也沒法繼續了
I'm sorry, it's kind of a dealbreaker for me.
沒法繼續...
Dealbreaker...
沒法繼續
dealbreaker.
是工作  我得去演播室了
Ugh, it's work. I gotta get down to the studio.
阿肯色州一個男人向Siri求婚  她答應了
A man in arkansas proposed to Siri, and she said yes!
抱歉  我得走了
I'm sorry. I have to run.
你怎么說  我明晚能帶布雷特來嗎
But, what do you say? I can bring Brett here tomorrow night?
好吧  說實話我有點緊張
Okay, honestly, I'm a little nervous about this.
不用緊張
Don't be.
我們三個一定會很開心的
The three of us are gonna have so much fun together!
好好休息吧  布雷特很磨人的
Now rest up. Brett can really wear you out.
喬什  你有不用的家具嗎
Josh, is there any furniture that you don't need in here?
因為我明天就要
Because I am signing the lease
租下我的兩臥公寓了
on my new two-bedroom apartment tomorrow...
你怎么了
What's going on with you?
你不會相信肖娜
You will never believe the bomb
昨晚跟我說了什么的
that Shauna dropped on my last night.
她終于跟你說了布雷特嗎
Oh, did she finally tell you about Brett?
沒錯  你怎么知道他的
Yeah! How do you know about Brett?
淡定  好嗎  這不是什么大事
Calm down, okay? It's not that big a deal.
可能對有的人不是
Maybe not for some guys.
你不是那些人
You are not some guys.
你不會面對戀愛里第一個問題[曲線球]
You're not gonna freak out at the first curveball
就措手不及的
your relationship throws you.
曲線[女人]我不怕  我怕的是球[男人]啊
I'm fine with the curves. It's the balls I'm worried about.
加比  約會真的很棒
Gabi, the date was perfect!
我們最后在廚房地板上啪啪了
It ended with sex on the kitchen floor.
迪米特里一定挺有本事
Dmitri must have some moves.
他把你哄得高興嗎
Did he have you on your bee's knees?
迪米特里  我說的是科爾曼
Dmitri? I'm talking about Coleman.
你讓他吃醋的計劃起效了
Your plan to make him jealous worked.
-我又搬回去啦  -不
- Girl, I'm moving back in. - No!
真是糟糕...你這么快就原諒他
That's awful...ly fast for you to forgive him.
你得再和迪米特里約一次會
You have to go on another date with Dmitri.
-為什么  -因為租...
Why would I do that? Because of the lease...
最...起碼你還能讓他繼續吃醋
it's the "lease" you could do to keep him super jealous.
加比  我知道你不習慣自己能出好主意
Gabi, I know you're not used to one of your plans working,
但現在是你該高興的時候
but this is the part where you should be happy!
是啊  我很高興
Oh, yeah, I'm totally happy.
一個小問題  一臺九成新的
Hey, quick question. Can I interest you
毛巾加熱器你感興趣嗎
in some slightly used towel warmers?
尤蘭達和科爾曼復合了嗎
Yolanda's back with Coleman?
天啊  迪米特里會發現的
Oh my god, Dmitri's gonna find out.
我們租不到那公寓了
We're not gonna get that apartment
雅各布森太太死得好冤
and Mrs. Jacobsen died for nothing.
行了  聽著  我們還能補救
Stop, okay, listen. We can still save this.
只要保證迪米特里在我們明早
We just have to make sure that Dmitri doesn't call Yolanda
簽租約之前不聯系尤蘭達就好
until after we sign the lease tomorrow morning.
算了  有什么用呢  都結束了
Stop it, okay. What's the point? It's over.
我去最后看一眼加斯頓  和他吻別
I'm just gonna go take one last look and kiss Gaston goodbye.
加斯頓是誰
Uh, who is Gaston?
洗碗機
The dishwasher.
我給他取了名字
I named him.
金發女
Blonde one!
我需要建議
I need advice.
我該請尤蘭達去納帕的紅酒間諜之旅嗎
Should I invite Yolanda for wine and spy experience in the Napa?
一般為"紅酒溫泉之旅"
我有優惠券
I have groupon.
聽著  迪米特里  我有話要說
Listen, Dmitri, I have to tell you something.
尤蘭達不喜歡你
Yolanda doesn't like you.
浴缸里還有噴水龍頭
There are jets in the bathtub!
她愛你
She loves you.
-真的嗎  -沒錯
- Really? - Uh, yes.
但我們發誓保密
But, we were sworn to secrecy.
所以別告訴她是我說的  好嗎
So, you can't tell her that I told you, okay?
就...你懂的...不要
It just-- you know, just don't-- actually,
干脆你就別跟她說話了
you know what, don't talk to her at all.
如果她愛我我為什么不跟她說話
What? Why I no talk if she's in love?
因為在美國你打電話給女人之前
Because in America you have to wait three days
要等三天的
before calling a woman.
否則看起來就很猴急
Otherwise you look needy.
但我不想等
But, I don't want to wait.
在俄羅斯  我們有句話
In Russia, we have saying,
"事不宜遲  否則凍死"
"You snooze, you freeze to death."
我們現在是在美國
Well, we live in America.
所以如果你想讓尤蘭達把你當成男人
So, if you want Yolanda to think you're a man,
就周一之后再打電話給她
you know, just don't call her until after Monday.
你們美國佬真是麻煩
You Americans so confusing.
我向我第一任妻子求婚
With my first wife, I ask her to marry me,
她說"呃"  第二天早上我們就結婚了
she say "Eh." Next morning we married.
好了  來吧
Okay. Here we go.
《阿比阿弟的激情冒險》
Bill and Ted's Sexcellent Adventure.
我們來看看兩男一女到底怎么回事
Let's see what this whole two guys one girl stuff is about.
或許沒那么糟呢
Maybe it's not so bad.
很糟
It is bad.
那女的夾在片子里干什么呢
Eww, what's that girl doing in there?
記得布雷特嗎  肖娜背著我劈腿的那家伙
Remember Brett? Guy Shauna's cheating on me with?
他們正在過來要和我3P
They're on their way over here to have a threesome with me.
真的嗎
Really?
作為你的公關  我覺得這樣不行
Well, as your publicist, I think that's a bad idea.
但作為朋友  上吧姑娘
But, as your friend, you go, girl.
我答應只是因為肖娜那么酷炫
Look, I only said yes because Shauna's so cool.
我不想顯慫
I didn't want to seem uncool,
但我就是慫啊  艾略特  我怕那樣
but I am uncool, Elliot. I am uncool in that way.
其他樣子  我還是很酷炫的
In every other way, I am cool.
喬什  振作一點
Josh, pull yourself together.
-他們來了  -好吧
- That's them. - Okay, look.
你出去告訴他們我不想這樣  好嗎
Go out there and tell them I can't do this, okay?
-就說太難了  -太難了
- Just go-- it's too hard. - Too hard.
不  我...
No, I--
別這么說  說我反悔了
Don't say that. Uh, I gotta back out.
反悔了
Back out.
這更...  艾略特
That's even-- Elliot!
說我在工作  你出去告訴他們我在工作
I'm working. You go out and there and you tell them I'm working.
艾略特  這是我兒子  布雷特
Hey, Elliot, meet my son, Brett.
這就是布雷特嗎
This is Brett?
還有你的新玩具
And there's one of your new toys.
這下一定很有趣
Well, this is gonna be funny.
他們走了嗎
Are they gone?
抱歉  喬什  但你最好還是出去
Sorry, Josh, but you should go out there.
布雷特很可愛的
Brett is cute.
或許比你還可愛
Might even be cuter than you.
看  我就怕這個
See, that's the problem!
要么我是那個多余的
Either I'm gonna be second banana,
要么他是那個多余的
or he's gonna be second banana.
無論如何  都多了個人啊
Either way, it's too many bananas!
你自己去說吧
Well, tell them yourself.
但溫柔點
But, be nice.
我覺得如果你傷害了他感情  布雷特會哭的
I get the sense that if you hurt his feelings, Brett might cry.
我經歷過
Been there.
喬什  我想讓你見見...
Hi, Josh. I want you to meet--
肖娜
Shauna...
抱歉  我做不來
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
這是我兒子  布雷特
This is my son, Brett.
我生命里的另一個男人
The other man in my life.
布雷特  這是喬什
Brett, this is Josh.
你好  喬什  想看我的卡車嗎
Hi, Josh. Do you want to see my truck?
布雷特
Oh, Brett!
你真是個可愛的小家伙
You are an adorable little man!
叔叔給你買輛真卡車
I'm gonna buy you a real truck.
好  一切就緒
Okay, everything's ready.
簽字的筆有了  慶祝的香檳有了
Pens ready to sign, champagne ready to pop.
唯一缺的就是帶著租約的迪米特里
Well, the only thing missing is Dmitri with the lease,
可他說好9點整會來的
and he said he'd be here at 9:00.
淡定  才9:02呢
Relax, it's only 9:02.
有這兩分鐘
That is two extra minutes
我們都能租下那公寓了
we could have been renting that apartment.
天啊  是他
Oh my god, that's him.
你好  迪米特里
Hey, Dmitri!
你有何貴干呀  對哦
What are you doing here? Oh, right!
是來和我們簽租約的
You're here to help us sign the lease.
是啊
Right.
交出來
Give it.
你想我用哪支筆呢
So, which pen should I use?
我有圓珠筆  簽字筆  香味記號筆
I'm thinking a ball point, roller ball, scented marker,
閃粉筆  還有一根筷子
glitter pen, ooh, a chopstick!
我的腎上腺素注射筆
My epipen!
不用筆
No pen!
因為俄國傳統是用血簽字嗎
Because it's a Russian custom to sign in blood?
我們沒問題的哦
Because we are fine with that.
你們沒問題嗎  我可有問題
Are you fine? Because Dmitri not so fine.
你說別打電話給尤尤斯基  我就不打
You tell me not to call Yoyoski, I no call.
但我也是個熱血青年  所以我帶著
But I am passionate man, so I go to her house
伏特加和熏鮭魚登門拜訪她
bearing gifts of vodka and smoked salmon.
天惹
Oh, boy.
然后她和男朋友吵起來了
And she get in huge fight with boyfriend.
天惹
Oh, boy.
回家路上我就在想你們為什么要騙我
All the way home I thinking why would girls lie to me?
然后  我恍然大悟
And then, it hit me like a ton of brick.
你們操縱我好得到公寓
You manipulate me to get apartment!
你們這些壞姑娘
You bad girls!
聽著  迪米特里  我們真的很抱歉
Well, listen, Dmitri, we're really, really sorry.
是  請讓我們補償你吧
Yes, please let us make it up to you.
你們別想要公寓了
No. No apartment for you!
我租給別人了
I give to someone else.
配得上那公寓的人
Someone who deserve it.
什么  不要啊  是誰
What? No! Who?
有筆嗎
Got a pen?
這是我吃過最美味的"道歉味"炸魷魚圈了
Now that was the best "I'm sorry" calamari I've ever had.
那你原諒我們把你生活搞得一團糟了嗎
So, you forgive us for totally screwing up your life?
某些角度來說  你們幫了我忙
Well, in a way, you two girls did me a favor.
科爾曼被迪米特里氣昏了頭
Coleman got so mad about Dmitri,
最后承認自己真的跟那服務員有一腿
he wound up admitting he did cheat with the waitress.
還有他的發型師
And his hairdresser.
他的遛狗員
And the dogwalker.
我們根本沒養狗
We don't even have a dog!
好了  第一個電影之夜我們看什么呢  鄰居
Okay, so what are we watching for our first movie night, neighbor?
我從喬什辦公室拿來的  經典電影
I grabbed it from Josh's office. It's a classic.
《阿比阿弟的冒險》
Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure.
美國1989年上映電影
基努·里維斯與亞歷克斯·溫特主演
我還不知道基努是黑人呢
I didn't know Keanu was black.
為什么大家都沒穿衣服
Why is everybody naked?
他們在那電話亭里真是火熱啊
They are really steaming up that phone booth.
遙控器給我
Gimme that remote.
聲音調大點
I gotta turn this up.
我們三個壞姑娘
We are bad girls!